[{"answer": "Hi, it's my friend. Listen, I was just talking to my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I think I deserve an explanation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, this is my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm my friend, I tell jokes for a living, but there's no joking about the financial crisis at that place. Show us you care. Call in your pledge now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, I know you are", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, but, you see, I saved something! See? I can save. I'll see you at the pledge drive, ok? my friend enters as my friend leaves", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, they're old cards from my grandmother", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The rule is a minimum of two days", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm making it up", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What, you think I eat all my meals with you?  Excuse me, sweetheart? I think you may have overcharged us. What is this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Got it.  Did you just see what happened here", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Channel eleven? Forgive me for trying to class up this place, for trying to have the that place reach another strata of society that might not watch channel eleven. my friend begins eating a candy bar with knife and fork", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I am eating my dessert. How do you eat it, with your hands", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I don't believe it, she did it again", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "She had an itch. She could have used any one of those fingers. That finger was meant for me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What are you doing", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Missing", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's not necessary", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I can't, I can't take it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I can't, I can't take it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pledge-Drive.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Uncle my friend, I don't want to have it", "qsentId": 24}]